eflorist.com 2006-12-07

# Privacy Policy for Find A Florist powered by Teleflora

**Privacy Policy for Find A Florist**

* * *

**Effective as of October 28, 2004**

Please take a moment to review the terms of our Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. 

**AGGREGATE INFORMATION** From time to time, we may collect general, non-personal, statistical information about the use of the Site, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on the Site, how long visitors stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, visitors "click" on. We collect this information in order to determine which areas of the Site are most popular and to enhance the Site for visitors. We may also group this information into aggregate visitor data in order to describe the use of the Site to our existing or potential business partners, sponsors, advertisers or other third parties, or in response to a government request. However, please be assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors to the Site.  

**  
PERSONAL INFORMATION** **Collection and Use:** From time to time, in order to access certain information and features contained on the Site, we may require you to register for an account on the Site and/or provide personal information such as your name, or e-mail address. We need to collect this information for fulfilling services and ensuring compliance with our policies and applicable law. 

We may use your personal information to customize the services we provide to you and send you periodic communications by e-mail or regular mail. For example, we may ask for your feedback regarding the Site or provide you with promotional or other special offers. If you choose to opt out of receiving any communications from us, you may uncheck the box on the registration form that says, "I would like to receive news and special offers from findaflorist.com". You may also opt out of receiving promotional or similar e-mails from us at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each such e-mail that we send to you. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information:** We may sometimes use other businesses to perform certain services for us, such as sending postal mail and providing marketing assistance and data analysis. We may provide personal information to those businesses when that information is necessary for them to complete a requested transaction or otherwise perform their duties. In addition, unless you have opted out of receiving e-mail offers from us as set forth above, we may sometimes share your e-mail address or other personal information with our sister companies within the Roll International Corporation family of companies, and our sister companies may send you periodic communications that we believe will be of interest to you. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personal information with any third parties. 

As the Roll International Corporation family of companies develops, we may buy other businesses or the assets of other businesses or sell our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that our business or all of its assets are acquired, customer information would be one of the transferred assets. 

Finally, we reserve the right to disclose visitor information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other visitors, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. This includes our right to exchange information with other organizations in order to protect against fraud and to reduce credit risk. We also reserve the right to disclose visitor information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

**  
IP ADDRESSES** An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, the big computers that "serve up" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to track the use of the Site. When visitors request pages from the Site, our servers log the visitors' IP addresses. It is not our practice to link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a visitor's session will be logged, but the visitor remains anonymous to us. However, we reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify a visitor only when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the Site's policies or to protect our service or customers, the Site, or others. 

**  
COOKIES** Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at the Site. The use of cookies is an industry standard. You'll find them at most Web sites. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Information such as the total number of visitors and pages viewed is most easily tracked with cookies. We may use the information from cookies to make improvements and updates to the Site and to tailor our services to our visitors' needs. 

You always have the option of disabling cookies using your browser preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, please be aware that some features of the Site may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. We do not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. 

**  
LINKS TO OTHER SITES; "PUBLIC" AREAS  
** Please be aware that when you are on the Site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from the Site's pages that take you outside our Site. These other sites may send their own cookies to visitors, collect data or solicit personal information. The privacy policies of these other sites may be significantly different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there. 

**  
SECURITY** Protecting the security of your personal information is very important to us. If you register with us, your online account information is protected by a password chosen by you. Access to that online account requires your username and password. We recommend that you do not disclose your username and password to any other person. When you transmit personal information from your PC to our servers, your information is also protected by both a "firewall" (a combination of computer hardware and software that helps keep unauthorized visitors from accessing information within our computer network) and industry standard SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. Once we receive your transmission, we will take reasonable precautions to ensure its security on our systems. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information. 

**  
PRIVACY POLICY FOR MINORS** We do not knowingly collect information from minors. If you are under 18, please do not provide any personal information to us. 

**  
CHANGES TO THESE TERMS** The terms of this Privacy Policy may change from time to time without prior notice to you, so please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

**  
QUESTIONS** Teleflora's findaflorist.com  
11444 West Olympic Boulevard, 4th floor  
Los Angeles, California 90064  
Attention: General Counsel  
Copyright © 2006 Teleflora, LLC. All rights reserved.
